fanmail.biz 2019-05-23

# ★ FanMail.biz: Privacy Statement

**Privacy Policy:**

Fanmail.biz has created this privacy policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: Fanmail.biz

Collected Information:

Fanmail.biz, through sign up processes, collects publisher information (name, address, phone, fax, email & URL), which is used solely for billing, payout, and marketing purposes. 

Non-Disclosure:

Fanmail.biz is committed to protecting the privacy of our publishers, advertisers, and website visitors. Fanmail.biz does not disclose any of the gathered information to third parties. While Fanmail.biz cannot fully control the actions of their website publishers, Fanmail.biz does require full disclosure of each site's privacy guidelines for every site that serves Fanmail.biz. 

Information Use:

If Fanmail.biz, Inc, for any reason uses the personal information that publishers/advertisers have provided, written permission will be obtained before doing so. The only exception to this will be the use of a publisher's company name and/or logo while finding advertising to be used on their site, or to promote the Fanmail.biz network. 

Third Party Advertising:

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp). 

Advertisers:

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. Some customer data is shared with the advertising companies. 

Information Automatically Logged:

We use your IP address for other purposes. 

Third Party Cookies:

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser. 

Cookies:

Our Site uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. 

Personal Information:

This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes. 

External Links:

This site contains links to other sites. Fanmail.biz.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Copyrights:

The published images as well as the other information in this Web, have been extracted of sites where they were offered gratuitously and therefore are property of their respective creators. The material is not used commercially by any of the organizations related directly to this site. If some image has copyright that prohibe its publication, send us an e-mail and we will retire it immediately. 

Opt Out

You can opt out of sharing your personal information with the Fanmail.biz, being contacted by the Fanmail.biz for promotional purposes, or having your Personal Information disclosed to third parties for such third parties’ marketing use. To exercise your choice to opt out, simply check or un-check the appropriate box on the form or web page on which you are providing your personal information, or you may always update your opt-out preferences in your web Site account (if any and if applicable) or by contacting the Fanmail.biz by following the instructions set forth in the Contact Us section of this Privacy Policy below. From each of its promotional e-mails, Fanmail.biz also enables you to opt-out of receiving future promotional emails from the Fanmail.biz. Please understand that if you opt out of receiving promotional correspondence from us, we may still contact you in connection with your relationship, activities, transactions and communications with us. Also, a request to have us stop sharing your personal information with other entities for marketing purposes will only apply as of the date of your request, and we will not be responsible for any communications that you may receive from entities that received your personal information prior to such request. In these cases, please contact that entity directly. 

Contacting the Web Site:

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: admin@fanmail.biz
